guidingtech.com 2016-11-18

# Terms Of Use - Guiding Tech

The following page lists the various policies/terms of use for Guiding Tech. Click on a link to check the corresponding policy or scroll down to read them one by one.

  1. Copyright Policy
  2. Privacy Policy
  3. Comment Policy
  4. Affiliate Links Disclosure
  5. Disclaimer and Disclosure

**Copyright Policy**

Guiding Tech by [Guiding Tech](http://www.guidingtech.com/) is licensed under a [Creative Commons Attribution-Noncommercial 2.5 India License](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/2.5/in/).

**Attribution Non-Commercial**

Guiding Tech makes its original content available under a Creative Commons Attribution Non-Commercial License, for non-commercial reproduction with credit to the source site.

This license permits anyone to do the following with original content on Guiding Tech, in any medium:

To reproduce, remix, or otherwise alter original Guiding Tech site material so long as the logo is displayed and credit is given. This includes, specifically, permission:

  * to reproduce articles
  * to reproduce screenshots of any page of the site
  * to include original Guiding Tech material in mash-ups, mixes, parodies, caricatures, etc for movies, TV, print or online

Guiding Tech makes no representations or guarantees about the suitability for third-party use of content that appears on the site, and licenses herewith only the content of which Guiding Tech is the copyright holder.

The above mentioned policy applies to Guiding Tech’s RSS Feed too and any other medium through which Guiding Tech publishes content.

**Privacy Policy**

The privacy of our visitors to Guiding Tech is important to us.

At Guiding Tech, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit Guiding Tech, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on Guiding Tech to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/).

**DoubleClick DART cookies**

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

**Comment Policy**

In order to make our comments useful and interesting, the following guidelines have been established for comment users:

  * Do not post threatening, harassing, defamatory, or libelous material.
  * Do not intentionally make false or misleading statements.
  * Do not offer to sell or buy any product or service.
  * Do not post material that infringes copyright.
  * Do not post information that you know to be confidential or sensitive or otherwise in breach of the law.
  * Keep all comments relevant to the article on the site where the comment is being posted.

Guiding Tech will not accept responsibility for information posted in the comments. Guiding Tech also reserves the right to delete any comment if it finds it to be inappropriate or if it is not following the comment policy.

**Affiliate Links Disclosure**

Although we primarily talk about free apps and tools, we write about useful paid apps too. And sometimes we use affiliate links for these products. It helps us make a small commission out of the sales if our readers were to buy them. This does not affect our editorial integrity though, and we tend to write about only the apps and products that we know will benefit our readers. After all, if the apps are not great, why would a reader want to buy it anyway? Our allegiance and loyalty is only to our readers and we only write about stuff that’s of top quality and useful, paid or not.

**Disclaimer& Disclosure**

Here at Guiding Tech, we aim to publish articles and other forms of content like video and audio with a motive to help out our readers in solving their computer related issues. We also aim to introduce our readers to new web apps and tools that could make their lives easier.

However, we do not guarantee that the tips, tricks, how to articles or guides we publish will help you or work on your computer. Different computers have different configurations and what works at our computers may not work on yours. Hence whenever you follow our advice or follow the instructions mentioned in the content on this site, you are doing that at your own risk and Guiding Tech will not be held responsible for any negative outcome of your action.

We also monetize our content with the help of advertisements and affiliate links wherever possible. We try to ensure that only genuine products are promoted through the ads and affiliate links but we cannot guarantee their authenticity because we use third-party ad servers and ad agencies, and hence we do not always have control over the kind of ads and affiliate products that get promoted on the site.
